Contact

rlpucely@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/randi-pucely-msn-np-c-24680355 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Trauma Surgery
Pediatric Intensive Care
Registered Nurses

Certifications

Nurse Practitioner

Randi Pucely, MSN, NP-C

Nurse Practitioner at Kaiser Permanente

Hawaiian Islands

Summary

Graduate of the Family Nurse Practitioner program at the George Washington University. AANP Board Certified. Working as a NP in the pediatric emergency room, as well as in a telehealth setting. Experience as an inpatient hospitalist for COVID-19 pandemic.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente Nurse Practitioner July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) San Diego, CA

Telehealth provider for KP members in the southern California region.

Rady Children's Hospital-San Diego Nurse Practitioner March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) San Diego, California

Krucial Staffing
Advanced Practice Nurse
April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)
New York, New York, United States

Nurse practitioner with hospitalist team in a community hospital during COVID relief effort in New York City.

Hawaii Pacific Health RN April 2015 - July 2019 (4 years 4 months) Honolulu, HI

PICU RN

AMN Healthcare Travel RN August 2013 - July 2019 (6 years) Experiencing new cities while studying for the nurse practitioner certification exam!

CVS MinuteClinic

APRN

November 2015 - August 2018 (2 years 10 months)

Honolulu, Hawaii

Scottsdale Healthcare is now HonorHealth

RN

January 2015 - April 2015 (4 months)

Scottsdale, AZ

PICU RN with float to NICU and general pediatrics

Dell Children's Medical Cntr, Austin TX

RN

September 2014 - December 2014 (4 months)

Pediatric stepdown RN with float to PICU

St. Alexius Medical Center

RN

July 2014 - September 2014 (3 months)

Hoffman Estates, IL

PICU RN with float to adult and pediatric general care

Hawaii Pacific Health

RN

February 2014 - July 2014 (6 months)

Travel RN in the Pediatric ICU with float to NICU

New York Presbyterian Hospital

RN

May 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 4 months)

New York, NY

RN, Pediatric ICU, skin resource nurse

UW Hospitals and Clinics

RN

April 2011 - May 2012 (1 year 2 months)

RN, Step-down trauma surgery

Washington Hospital Center RN October 2009 - December 2010 (1 year 3 months) RN, Med-surg

Education

The George Washington University

MSN, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2010 - 2013)

Pace University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2008 - 2009)